http://www.pls-mc.com/company/privacy-policy/#visiting_our_website

E. Contact
A. Basic InformationThe protection of your privacy is very important to us. We place great emphasis on the protection of your personal data and your right to informational self-determination. In the following we, the PLS Programmierbare Logik & Systeme GmbH, inform about the collection and processing of personal data when using our website or our services at www.pls-mc.com. Personal data are all data that can be related to you personally, e.g. name, address, email address, user behavior.1. ControllerResponsible for data protection in accordance with No. 7 of Article 4 General Data Protection Regulation (ÑGDPRì):PLS Programmierbare Logik & Systeme GmbHTechnologieparkStraﬂe der Freundschaft 92DE-02991 LautaGermanyFurther information and contact data can be found in our imprint.2. Data Protection OfficerYou can contact our data protection officer at:Beratungshaus Jens ProtzeAn der Hauptstraﬂe 4aDE-04720 DˆbelnE-Mail: privacy@pls-mc.com3. Data SecurityPlease note that most data transmission via the internet is unsecured. There is a chance that transmitted information may become known to or might be even falsified by unauthorized parties. We protect our website and other systems by technical and organizational measures against loss, destruction, access, modification or distribution of your data by unauthorized persons. For secure communication with us, we offer encrypted communication via the SSL protocol as standard. To access your online customer account, you have to enter your user name and password. Be sure to keep your login information confidential and close the browser window once you have finished communicating with us, especially if you share your computer with others.In connection with access to our website, data that may allow identification (e.g. IP address) is temporarily stored on our servers for data and system security purposes, but in principle for no longer than thirty days. The processing of possibly personal data for data and system security purposes is carried out on the basis of point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR and our legitimate interest in securing our systems and preventing misuse.4. Principles for the storage and deletion of personal dataPersonal data will only be processed for the period required achieving the respective storage purpose or if this is provided for in the laws or regulations applicable to us, e.g. commercial or tax storage obligations. If a storage purpose or a legally prescribed storage period expires, affected personal data will be deleted routinely and in accordance with legal regulations or their processing will be restricted, e.g. limited processing within the scope of commercial or tax storage obligations.The processing of personal data on the basis of a legal obligation, namely the fulfilment of legal storage obligations, is based on point (c) of Article 6(1) GDPR. Insofar as personal data pursuant to point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR are processed for the purpose of preserving evidence, these processing purposes shall cease after expiry of the statutory limitation periods; the statutory regular limitation period is three years.For further details on specific storage and deletion periods, we also refer to individual service descriptions or information in this data protection declaration.
B. Visiting our website
If you merely use our website for information purposes, i.e. if you do not register or provide us elsewise with personal information, we may collect personal data that your browser transmits to our server.1. Technical provision of the websiteWhen you visit our website, we collect the following data, which is technically necessary for us to display our website and to guarantee the stability and security of our online offer:IP addressDate and time of the requestTime zone difference to Greenwich Mean Time (GMT)Content of the request (specific page)Access Status/HTTP Status Codethe amount of data transferred in each caseWebsite from which the request comesBrowserOperating system and its interfaceLanguage and version of the browser software.The legal basis for this collection and processing is point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the provision of a functional website offer and its system security. In addition, we use the aforementioned data in non-personal form for statistical purposes and to improve our online offering.2. CookiesWe use so-called ìcookiesî on various pages of our website to make the use of our website more comfortable and to enable certain functions. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a computer system via an internet browser.Many websites and servers use cookies. Cookies often contain a so-called Cookie-ID. Such an ID is a unique identification of the cookie and consists of a string of characters by which websites and servers can be assigned to a specific internet browser in which the cookie was stored. Such cookies make it possible to distinguish your individual browser from other internet browsers that contain other cookies. A particular internet browser can therefore be recognized and identified using a unique cookie ID.By using cookies, we can provide you with more user-friendly services that could not or only to a limited extent be implemented without cookies. Cookies enable us to recognize the users of our website. The purpose of this recognition is to make it easier for users of our online offer to use it. An illustrative example is the customerís user account, for which a cookie is required to implement some of the functions of our website and will exist only until you close your browser. The use of Cookies is based on point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR. In this respect, we have a legitimate interest in providing and optimizing a functional and convenient online offering.Overview about the necessary cookies used by this website
ID
Description
Technology
Expiration Date
Owner
accept_cookie
Consent to the cookie usage
Cookie
pls-mc.com
Cookie prevention and removementYou can prevent the setting of cookies by setting your internet browser and thus permanently object to the setting of cookies. In addition, cookies that have already been set can be deleted via an internet browser or other software programs. Please note, however, that you may not be able to use all functions of our and other online services if you deactivate cookies in your internet browser.3. Google Web FontsThis site uses so-called web fonts provided by Google Inc. (ÑGoogleì) to uniformly display fonts. When you call up a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.To do this, the browser you are using must connect to Google's servers. This gives Google knowledge that our website has been accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web Fonts is in the interest of a uniform and appealing presentation of our online offers. This represents a legitimate interest within the meaning of point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR.If your browser does not support web fonts, a default font is used by your computer. Further information about Google Web Fonts can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google's privacy policy: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.4. Web ScriptsThis site uses so-called web script libraries. When you call up a page, your browser loads the required web script library BootstrapCDN (https://www.bootstrapcdn.com/) into your browser execution unit to perform web functionality.To do this, the browser you are using must connect to web script library servers. This gives the web script hoster knowledge that our website has been accessed via your IP address. This represents a legitimate interest within the meaning of point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR.Further information about BootstrapCDN can be found at BootstrapCDN's privacy policy: https://www.bootstrapcdn.com/privacy-policy/.
C. Use of Services
1. Customer AccountOn our website we offer a customer account for which you can voluntarily register. This requires certain data from you. The required fields are marked accordingly in the registration form. Within the customer account you have the possibility to download the latest UDE program version, UDE manuals and the UDE product information.The legal basis for processing is point (b) of Article 6(1) GDPR. If you remove your customer account, we delete your data as far as the storage is no longer necessary (e.g. due to legal storage obligations).Marketing and Market ResearchWe also use address data (title, surname, first name, address) for our own marketing purposes. In this context you can, for example, receive information about new products, special offers and discounts from our range by mail. This data processing is carried out in accordance with point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR on the basis of justified interests in optimising our range of products and services as well as advertising.If personal data is processed for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of your personal data for the purpose of such advertising; this also applies to profiling, insofar as it is associated with such direct marketing.2. Use of contactOn our website we offer you various ways to get in touch with us and to send us messages. In particular, you can contact us by telephone or by email. In addition to that, on our website you can request a quote, a Callback or information via different contact forms . The respective mandatory fields are marked accordingly. If you contact us accordingly, we will store and process the data you provide (e.g. your email address, name and telephone number etc.) in order to process your request.The legal basis in this respect is point (b) of Article 6(1) GDPR . We delete the accruing data after the storage is no longer necessary, or limit the processing if statutory retention obligations exist. In addition, when using the contact forms, we collect the IP address of the calling computer as well as the date and time of dispatch. The legal basis for this is point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in securing our systems and preventing misuse.3. NewsletterIf you subscribe to our newsletter, we collect and process personal data for sending you advertising information, e.g. information about our products, on events and special offers or campaigns of our company.The subscription is based on consent. Only your email address is mandatory. You can give us the further information (name, company) voluntarily so that we can address you personally. For the subscription to our newsletter we use the so-called double opt-in procedure. This means that after your subscription we will send you an email to the email address you provided, in which we ask you to confirm that you wish to receive our newsletter via the email address you provided.We use your data transmitted for the subscription to the newsletter exclusively for the purpose of the delivery of our newsletter. The legal basis for the processing of your data for the purpose of carrying out the newsletter service is your consent in accordance with point (a) of Article 6(1) and 7 GDPR. In addition, the following data is collected upon registration: IP address of the calling computer, date and time of registration. This data is collected and stored in order to demonstrate that effective consent has actually been given by the respective user and that the double opt-in procedure has been properly carried out. The legal basis is point (f) of Article 6(1) GDPR, whereby our legitimate interests lie in the demonstrability of the proper collection and/or execution of the double opt-in procedure.The data collected when subscribing to the newsletter will only be stored as long as the subscription to the newsletter is active and we need the certain data for evidentiary purposes. You may unsubscribe from our newsletter service at any time via the unsubscribe link in the received newsletter or via the account settings in your customer account. You can also contact us, using your email address registered for the newsletter, under support@pls-mc.com or the contact information in Section "E. Contactî of this Privacy Policy.
D. Rights of data subjects
We would like to inform you about your rights under the GDPR as "data subject". As a data subject you have the following rights with respect to the personal data that concerns you:Right to information (Art. 15 para. 1, 2 GDPR)Right to rectification (Art. 16 GDPR) or to erasure (Art. 17 GDPR)Right to restriction of processing (Art. 18 GDPR)Right to data portability (Art. 20 GDPR)Right to object to processing (Art. 21 GDPR)Right to withdraw consent (Art. 7 para. 3 GDPR)Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (Art. 77 GDPR)In addition, we summarise for you the key points of the rights of data subjects under the GDPR as follows, although this description does not claim to be exhaustive, but merely addresses the basic features of the rights of affected persons under the GDPR:Right to information (including right to confirmation and rights to data provision)The data subject has the right to obtain from the controller confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning him or her are being processed.The data subject has the right of access to personal data concerning him/her and to the following information:the purposes of the processing;the categories of personal data concerned;the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations;if possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored or, if this is not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;the existence of the right to request from the controller rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing of personal data concerning the data subject or to object to such processingthe right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;if the personal data are not collected from the data subject, any available information as to their source;the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred to in Article 22 para. 1 and 4 GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and the envisaged consequences of such processing for the data subjectthe right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards pursuant to Article 46 GDPR relating to the transfer, where personal data are transferred to a third country or to an international organisation.The data subject has the right to receive a copy of the personal data undergoing processing of him/her.Right to rectificationThe data subject has the right to optain from the controller without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning him/her. Taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject has the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statementRight to restriction of processingThe data subject has the right to obtain from the controller restriction of processing where one of the following applies:the accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject, for a period enabling the controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data,the processing is unlawful and the data subject opposes the erasure of the personal data and requests the restriction of their use instead;the controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; orthe data subject has objected to processing pursuant to Article 21(1) GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of the controller override those of the data subject.Right to erasure ('right to be forgottenë)In principle and subject to certain legal requirements for data processing (cf. exception Article 17 para. 3 GDPR), the data subject has the right to obtain from the controller the erasure of personal data concerning him/her without undue delay and the controller has the obligation to erase personal data without undue delay where one of the following grounds applies:the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed.the data subject withdraws consent on which the processing is based according to Article 6 para. 1 lit. a, or Article 9 para. 2 lit. a GDPR, and where there is no other legal ground for the processing.the data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21 para. 1 GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or the data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21 para. 2 GDPR.The personal data have been unlawfully processed.the personal data have to be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject.the personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services referred to in Article 8 para. 1 GDPR.Right to data portabilityThe data subject has the right to receive the personal data concerning him/her which he/she has provided to a controller in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the controller to which the personal data have been provided, if the processing is based on an consent or on a contract in accordance with Article 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR and the processing is carried out by means of automated means.In exercising his/her right to data portability, the data subject shall have the right to have the personal data transferred directly by a data controller to another data controller, where this is technically feasible.Right to withdrawThe data subject has the right to withdraw his/her consent at any time. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authorityEvery data subject has the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of his/her habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement, if the data subject considers that the processing of personal data relating to him/her infringes the GDPR.The supervisory authority for data protection responsible for us is:Der S‰chsische DatenschutzbeauftragteDevrientstraﬂe 1DE-01067 DresdenGermanySeparate reference to the right to object pursuant to Art. 21 para. 1, 2 GDPRYou have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to processing of personal data concerning you which is based on Article 6 para. 1 lit. e or f GDPR, including profiling based on those provisions.If you object, we will no longer process the personal data unless we demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms of or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.Where personal data are processed for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to processing of personal data concerning you for such marketing, which includes profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing.
E. Contact
You can contact us at any time for the exercise of your rights as well as for general questions regarding data protection by sending us an email to privacy@pls-mc.com or by using the other contact information provided under point A in this Privacy Policy.Further information and contact data can be found in our imprint.
Contact
Information:info@pls-mc.comTechnical Support:support@pls-mc.comSales Department:sales@pls-mc.comPhone: + 49 35722 384 - 0
This website uses only necessary cookies.
Read more about the usage of cookies in the Privacy Policy of this website.
